enduringword.com 2019-03-31

# Enduring Word Bible Commentary Privacy Policy

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the www.enduringword.com and Enduring Word Media and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Enduring Word Media include www.enduringword.com and Enduring Word Media. By using the Enduring Word Media website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

**Collection of your Personal Information**

We do not collect personally identifiable information from our users. We may gather personal or non-personal information in the future.

Enduring Word Media may automatically collect information about your computer hardware and software This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain the quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Enduring Word Media website. Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Enduring Word Media’s public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.

Enduring Word Media encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Enduring Word Media so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Enduring Word Media is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Enduring Word Media website.

**Use of Cookies**

The Enduring Word Media website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Enduring Word Media pages, or register with Enduring Word Media site or services, a cookie helps Enduring Word Media to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Enduring Word Media website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Enduring Word Media features that you customized. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Enduring Word Media services or websites you visit.

**Children Under Thirteen**

Enduring Word Media does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

**Opt-Out & Unsubscribe**

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from Enduring Word Media by contacting us from the contact information below.

**Changes to this Statement**

Enduring Word Media will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Enduring Word Media encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Enduring Word Media is protecting your information.

**Contact Information**

Enduring Word Media welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Enduring Word Media has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Enduring Word Media at:
